<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on horse life 98</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on horse life 98</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Horse Life 98 © 2019-2021 J. P. Savard</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 02:55:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yukiis.moe/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>brb</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/brb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 02:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/brb/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m taking a break. Again. Yeah, I only managed to last 8 strips this time, but eh. Life&amp;rsquo;s been hard these days, and while it made me draw more, which is a good thing, especially with season 4 of HL98 which is the first one I didn&amp;rsquo;t use a character creator, as I made everything from scratch, I didn&amp;rsquo;t really had time for deadlines so&amp;hellip; yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m just going back to posting whenever, I guess.</description></item><item><title>guess who's back</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/guess-whos-back/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/guess-whos-back/</guid><description>Well. We&amp;rsquo;re back with new comics every Tuesday in a brand new style, I guess.
Also I started posting the comics on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and Patreon, the latter of which you can pay $1 a month on there to see said comics before everyone else! I never bothered to do this before as I used to always finish the week&amp;rsquo;s comic on Mondays 11:58pm, like 2 minutes before it goes live on the site but nowadays I end up finishing it on Thursday or Friday instead so yeah, that might be worth it&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>I failed</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/i-failed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 03:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/i-failed/</guid><description>Horse Life 98 Paneltober is going for a small break. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I&amp;rsquo;m going to pick it off from where I left shortly. Have a good day :)</description></item><item><title>paneltober</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/paneltober/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 03:26:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/paneltober/</guid><description>Start the story from here!
Hey guess what? It&amp;rsquo;s October, and you know what this means? ONE PANEL EVERYDAY.
You probably know this meme where artists draw one drawing a day from a prompt list, and it&amp;rsquo;s called, uh, somethingtober? Yeah, let&amp;rsquo;s do the same thing this month. Paneltober. One panel a day, with a story to follow. Gonna be epic.
Unfortunately, the guy who made up the whatevertober meme was apparently accused for some nasty stuff like stealing someone else&amp;rsquo;s stuff to capitalize on his brand, so it&amp;rsquo;s best to avoid the official list, but none of the alternate lists were appealing to me, so eh.</description></item><item><title>fanart</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/fanart/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 02:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/fanart/</guid><description>I managed to add a fanart gallery, so if you send fanart I&amp;rsquo;ll put it up there? I kinda hacked the WordPress theme so it works and won&amp;rsquo;t show up in the main comic archive, and it might break each time I update it, so eh, have fun. I already put most of the fanart of the Human Yuki era there, hope you like them, and be sure to support the artists!</description></item><item><title>schedule changes</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/schedule-changes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 02:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/schedule-changes/</guid><description>The comic moves to the &amp;ldquo;every Tuesday&amp;rdquo; schedule now, I guess. Had a pretty crazy weekend, so yeah. Might be better this way. Expect a new comic tomorrow, Tuesday.
Also, new URL? Yeah, why not.
Yuki is moe.
Enough said.</description></item><item><title>chapter 3</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/chapter-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 05:59:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/chapter-3/</guid><description>New chapter, new redesign. Or is it the other way around? Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s still the comic you know and love.
This comic always been about experimentation, using character creators as much as possible (along with my own drawings and photography when possible, to spice it up a bit). The first few comics used Pony Town characters in Microsoft Chat 2.5, then after a small hiatus my workflow upgraded to Adobe Illustrator and MikuMikuDance, after I experimented a bit with VRoid and the like.</description></item><item><title>wtf is a schedule</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/wtf-is-a-schedule/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 15:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/wtf-is-a-schedule/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s comic is gonna be late. Yeah, I know, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to stick to a &amp;ldquo;every Monday&amp;rdquo; schedule, but now I guess we&amp;rsquo;re back to the &amp;ldquo;post whenever I want&amp;rdquo; schedule. My workflow stopped working correctly (Windows&amp;rsquo;s a bitch I hate it), plus I just got a new, proper office job getting in the way (except I&amp;rsquo;m still working at home due to the pandemic thing), so it&amp;rsquo;s gonna mess everything up.</description></item><item><title>new website</title><link>https://yukiis.moe/blog/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 01:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yukiis.moe/blog/hello-world/</guid><description>This comic was previously hosted in a separate category on my normal blog where I talk about random stuff not related with this at all, and I was bored of the default theme not adapted for a webcomic, so here it is. I moved everything to a new website. That is adapted to webcomics. With proper back and next buttons.
There&amp;rsquo;s still a few bugs and kinks here and there as I write this, and the design could be improved, but eh, it should still be way better than it was before.</description></item></channel></rss>